Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1921-2017 RL.00052
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal Materials, 1921-2017
  - Awards and Honorary Degrees, 1
    - Washington U. Honorary Degree, 1989 (Box 74)
  - Personal Items, 1921-2017; 2
    Includes personal items, scrapbooks, photographs, datebooks, rolodexes, and biographical materials, among other items.
    - Address Books, undated; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Areopagus, 1939-2005 (Box 74)
      Files for social club
    - Arrow: Birthday - 65th, 1986 (Box 74)
      Includes birthday greetings
    - Arrow: Birthday - 70th, 1991; 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Arrow: Birthday - 80th, 2001 (Box 74)
    - Arrow: Birthday - 90th, 2011 (Box 74)
    - Arrow in Beijing, 2009; 196 photographs derived from optical disc; 487 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
      Includes photographs
    - Arrow: Miscellaneous, 2014 (Box 74)
      Includes miscellaneous personal correspondence
    - Arrow: Personal - Economist Trading Cards, 1995 (Box 74)
    - Arrow: Photographs, 1967-1999; 3 folders (Box 74)
      Includes official university photographs and personal photographs
    - Arrow: Publications List, undated (Box 74)
    - Arrow: Vita, undated (Box 74)
    - Belgium, 1964 (Box 74)
      Includes travel notes
    - Biographical Material, 1968-1972; 2 folders (Box 74)
      Biographical sketch and some photographs
    - Birthday Congratulations, 1933 (Box 74)
      Notebook of congratulatory notes
    - City College Reunion, 1989-1997 (Box 74)
    - Crimson and Gold, 1936 (Box 74)
      Includes yearbook with signatures
    - Datebooks, 1975-2002 (Box 90)
    - Datebooks, 2003-2017 (Box 91)
    - Diploma, Degrees, and Certificates, 1936-1951 (Box 75)
      Includes diploma, graduate degrees, and certificates related to military service
    - Directories, 2007-2010 (Box 74)
    - Early Career, 1941-1960 (Box 74)
      Includes files related to Arrow's applications for actuarial jobs, undergraduate study at City College, graduate study at Columbia University, and files related to early work at the Cowles Commission, RAND Corporation, and Stanford
    - Event Posters, 2004-2008 (Box 77)
    - Finland, 1963 (Box 74)
    - Group Photo, undated (Box 77)
    - ID Cards, undated (Box 74)
    - Italy, 1993 (Box 80)
    - Japan, 1963 (Box 80)
    - Long Ridge, 1978 (Box 80)
      Files related to purchase and sale of Long Ridge Ranch
    - Microcosm 1940 (Volume 2)
      Yearbook of College of the City of New York. Includes signatures.
    - New York Times Birthday Book, 2008 (Box 77)
    - Nobel Newspaper Clippings, 1972; 3 folders (Box 80)
      Includes newspaper clippings announcing award of the Nobel to Arrow
    - Nobels: Nobel Laureates photographed by Peter Badge, 2008 (Volume 1)
      Book of photographs by Peter Badge. Published by Wiley-VCH
    - Oral History, 1990-2011 (Box 89)
      Includes oral history contributions to American Jewish Committee and Stanford Oral History Program
    - Passports, 1995-2005, 2015 (Box 80, Box 74)
      Includes expired passports
    - Personal Correspondence, 1972-1990 (Box 80)
    - Personal Event Albums, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 80)
      Albums of materials for events attended
    - Personal Files, 1943-2011; 2 folders (Box 80)
    - Personal History, 1940-1953; 2 folders (Box 80)
      Includes recommendation letters from Harold Hotelling and Abraham Wald, and records from military service
    - Personal items electronic records, 1999-2017; 313 files, 578 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
      Includes personal and family photographs.
    - Personal Miscellaneous, 1968-1972 (Box 80)
      Includes personal files
    - Personal Notebooks, 2008 (Box 80)
    - Personnel Security Information, 1950 (Box 80)
      Includes forms for government security clearance
    - Phone Numbers, undated (Box 80)
    - Portrait photograph, 2017 (Box 75)
      Professional portrait photograph
    - Prof. Kenneth J. Arrow in Shanghai Oct. 30, 2008; 35 photographs derived from optical disc; 30 MB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
    - Rolodexes, undated (Box 82)
    - Sale of Brooklyn Bridge, 2008 (Box 80)
      Commemorative document containing scrap of original wooden walkway
    - School Notebook, 1928-1929 (Box 80)
    - School of Meteorology, 1943 (Box 80)
      Includes yearbook for Army School of Meteorology
    - Scrapbook, 1921-2004; 5 folders (Box 80)
      Includes birth certificate, school records, and newspaper clippings from career highlights
    - Seidman Award Program, 1998 (Box 80)
    - Selections from Personal Library, 1926-2017 (Box 86)
      Includes books of economics and literature, some with signed dedications and inscriptions
    - Selections from Personal Library, 1890-2013 (Box 87)
    - Selections from Personal Library, 1898-1945 (Box 88)
    - Selections from Personal Library (Box 89)
      Includes Selma Arrow's thesis
    - Signed soccer ball, undated (Box 82)
      Origin of soccer ball is unclear
    - Stanford Hospital, 2004 (Box 80)
    - Testimonial Experience, undated (Box 80)
      List of expert witness testimony
    - Travel Journals, 1928-1929 (Box 80)
    - Travel Journals, 1931-2007; 5 folders (Box 81)
    - U.S. Army insignias and pins, personal items, 1982 and undated (Box 85)
    - Watercolor portrait of Arrow with caption in Japanese, undated (Box 77)
    - Yearbook, 1937 (Box 81)
      Includes signed yearbook